

DIMA OLEINIK

WEB-DEVELOPER

Contact



Ukraine, Nikolaev



+380636371367



https://doleinik-portfolio.netlify.app



doleinika@gmail.com

About Me

My name is Dima, I'm 24 years old.

Very purposeful and in a short time, thanks to his personal and professional qualities, he was able to achieve a good result, and I strive to learn more and more new technologies and develop in this.

Education

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

2016 - 2020

MNU Sukhomlynsky

Frontend Developer

2020 - 2020

BeetRoot Academy

Master`s Degree, English Language and Literature

2022 - Present

MNU Sukhomlynsky

Work Experience

Freelance

11.2020 - Present

Web developer

· Freelance website development

NextG

08.2021 - 11.2021

WordPress developer

- · Creation of sites from scratch
- · Support for written sites

Brightech

11.2021 - 07.2022

WordPress developer

- · Creation of sites from scratch
- · Support for written sites

Brightech

07.2022 - Present

Team Lead/Tech Lead

WordPress developer

- · Creation of sites from scratch
- Support for written sites
- · Team management
- Trainee Internship
- · Quality control
- Mentoring

\$ Skills

•••••

HTML/CSS Wordpress ••••• ••••• Scss/Sass **JavaScript** ••••• ••••• **BEM** PHP ••••• ••••• Gulp Node.js ••••• ••••• Gsap React ••••• ••••• MySQL Three.js

☑ Projects

Panorama

Americana Advisors

Balard

HedgeHog

TillaDelse

Hommondknol

Senior services of america

Brightech

Freight Alliance

Truit